ANDREI ZERNOV

Front End Software Engineer



Professional Portfolio: <u>andreizernov.netlify.app</u>
Shanghai, China | andrei.zernov@outlook.com | +8618616931363
<u>www.linkedin.com/in/andrei-zernov</u>/ | <u>www.github.com/AndreiZernov</u>|
WeChat ID: AndreiZernov

Front End Software Engineer with extensive knowledge of Networking and Cybersecurity Concepts. I have a Master's Degree in Business Management from Pacific National University and +5 years of working experience in an International Environment. My primary focus and inspiration for my studies are Web Development. In my free time, study UI, UX designs and App engineering. I am both driven and self-motivated and continuously experimenting with new technologies and techniques. Strive to better myself as a Web Developer, and the development community as a whole.

Technical Proficiencies



Projects

React Finder - React Web Application



www.react-finder.netlify.app



Application created for community as links to Free Helpful Resources, which cover React, React Native, Redux and GraphQl materials.

- Technology: React, GraphQl, Bootstrap 4, SASS, HTML5 and CSS3
- Integration of React Context and Hooks, Auth0 Authentication, Formspree and Contentful
- Animation created with Lottie, GSAP and CSS

MLTK Collection - React Web Application



www.multik.netlify.app/



React Progressive Web Application, Gallery of Projects and Photo Collection for Professional Photographer MLTK

- Technology: React, GraphQl, Bootstrap 4, SASS, HTML5 and CSS3
- Data management by the API content platform Contentful
- Animation created with ScrollMagic, GSAP libraries and CSS

React Finder App - IOS and Android Application



www.expo.io/@andrewzer/react-finder



React Finder Application created for community for IOS and Android platform.

- Technology: React, Redux, GraphQl, Styled Components, HTML5 and CSS3
- Integration of Firebase Authentication and Contentful Data Management API
- Project build by Expo framework for React Native IOS and Android
- Animation created with Lottie and CSS

Employment history

May 2018 to Present

Operations Manager | Beijing Starz International Management Co. | Shanghai, China

December 2016 to May 2018

Operations Manager | SECA Worldwide | Shanghai, China

June 2015 to November 2016

Operations Specialist | Gustav Company | Russia / Shanghai, China

Education and Training

Pacific National University, Russian Federation

Master's Degree in Business Management, 2015

Professional IT Certifications

Treehouse: Front End Web Development, React Javascript, Full Stack Javascript, Web Design

Freecodecamp: Responsive Web Design, JavaScript

Algorithms and Data Structures, Front End Libraries

CompTIA Security+ Certified
CompTIA Network+ Certified

CCNA Cisco Certified Network Associate







Additional Professional certificates in Cloud technology, Windows and Linux OS, Cybersecurity covered by Google, Microsoft learning, Coursera.org, EDX.org, Cybrary.it and Udacity.com